<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on janwillem.xyz</title>
    <link>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on janwillem.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://janwillem.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Everyday Carry</title>
      <link>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/edc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/edc/</guid>
      <description>I love reading what other people carry with them on a daily basis. So here is my list.
 Bag
The North Face Berkeley Satchel in black.
Watch
Casio Edifice EFS-S510L-1AVUEF Solar
Phone
iPhone 8+ in Space Grey with the standard Apple leather case in black.
Headphones
JBL T110 BT
Pen
Retro 51 Tornado Stealth
Notebook
Rhodia Blac No12 Lined
Shopping Bag
Susan Bijl shopping bag large</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2020</title>
      <link>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/2020-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/2020-02/</guid>
      <description>TV  The Man in the High Castle  S02 / S03 / S04
What a fantastic show! In the first couple of episodes I thought it was some kind of love story or something. But it turned in to some sci-fi stuff I absolutely love.
 Movies  Ready Player One  Read the book, liked it. Saw the movie in the cinema, left halfway, dit not like it at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Just Want To Play A Video Game...</title>
      <link>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/i-just-want-to-play-a-video-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/i-just-want-to-play-a-video-game/</guid>
      <description>Two days ago I had some spare time and thought: &amp;ldquo;Lets go play some Call Of Duty on the PlayStation!&amp;rdquo;
So I fired up the ol&amp;rsquo; PS4 and started playing within 2 minutes had to update the game. Fine. Click update. Wait? How big is the update? 15GB for 1 game update.
I have pretty fast internet, so the download doesn&amp;rsquo;t take that long. But guess what? After downloading, the PS4 has to copy the file to god knows where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iPad</title>
      <link>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/ipad/</guid>
      <description>Thinking more and more about making the iPad my main computing device. Not the Pro, don’t really see the point in owning one (besides the bigger screen), but my 2018 iPad.
The more I sit behind my MacBook (and the more stories I read about people who made the transition), the more I think: can’t I do this on my iPad? With a clicky keyboard. Obviously…
I’m looking for a small stand for the iPad, so it can stand up nicely on my desk and I don’t need to look down constantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Kart Tour</title>
      <link>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/mario-kart-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/mario-kart-tour/</guid>
      <description>Why the hell would you pay 5 dollar a month for a 200CC mode in Mario Kart?? There is no controller support and you can only play it in portrait mode.
 Rather amusingly, one of the in-app purchase options is a $4.99 subscription for extra items … the same price as Apple Arcade’s entire 100-game library.
 9 to 5 Mac</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Arcade First Impression</title>
      <link>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/apple-arcade-first-impression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://janwillem.xyz/posts/apple-arcade-first-impression/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I installed iOS 13 on my iPhone 8+. I also started the Apple Arcade trial.
As with all mobile games: touch controls suck. A lot. I played these games with my PS4 controller. Pairing it with my iPhone took 10 seconds: press the PS button and the share button on your controller at the same time, and hold it for a few seconds. Open the bluetooth settings on your phone and click on the Dualshock controller.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>